Finding Aid for the Rod Amateau Papers PASC.0088
UCLA Library Special Collections
Rod Amateau papers
1955-1966
UCLA Library Special Collections
Amateau, Rod
PASC.0088
9.2 Linear Feet (22 boxes)
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 994621823606533
Biography
Rodney Amateau was born Dec. 20, 1927 in New York, NY; staff writer, CBS radio; stage manager, Lux Radio Theatre; US Army, 1941; junior writer, test director, and 2nd unit director, 20th Century-Fox; television director for numerous shows including "Schlitz Playhouse Of Stars," "Four Star Playhouse," "General Electric Theatre," "Dennis Day Show," "Lassie," "Ray Milland Show," and "Bob Cummings Show"; director and producer for "Burns And Allen Show" and "Dobie Gillis."
Scope and Content
Collection consists of bound television series scripts including the "Bob Cummings Show" (1955-68), "Phil Silvers Show" (1963-64), "My Mother The Car" (1965-66), "George Burns And Gracie Allen Show" (1956-58), "George Burns Show" (1958-59), "Many Loves Of Dobie Gillis" (1959-63), "O.K. Crackerby!" 1965), and "Mister Ed" (1960).
Television producers and directors -- Archives.; Television broadcasting -- Employees -- Archives.; Amateau, Rod, 1923-2003--Archives
- BOB CUMMINGS SHOW, THE
  - Acid Test, The (Show #47, v.X)
    - Aired: 1/26/56. Draft script dated: 11/26/55. Writer(s): Henning, Paul * Shuken, Phil (Box 18)
  - Air Corps Versus Marriage (Show #17, v.VII)
    - Aired: 4/17/55. Draft script dated: 2/19/55. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Manhoff, Bill * Schiller, Bob / Weiskopf, Bob (Box 17)
  - Air Force Versus Navy (Show #60, v.V)
    - Aired: 5/3/56. Draft script dated: 3/9/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil (Box 17)
  - Air Force Versus Ruthie (Show #75, odd 1955-56)
    - Aired: 12/6/56. Draft script dated: 10/4/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil (Box 18)
  - Beautiful Psychologist, The (Show #69, odd 1955-56)
    - Aired: 11/1/56. Draft script dated: 8/24/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil (Box 18)
  - Bob Ages Margaret (Show #98, v.III, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 5/23/57. Draft script dated: 3/29/57. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil / Wesson, Dick (Box 16)
  - Bob Batches It (Show #68, v.VI)
    - Draft script dated: 8/17/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil (Box 17)
  - Bob Becomes Chuck's First Patient (Show #83, v.X)
    - Aired: 2/7/57. Draft script dated: 12/7/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil / Wesson, Dick (Box 18)
  - Bob Buys a Plane (Show #67, v.VI)
    - Aired: 10/11/56. Draft script dated: 5/11/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil (Box 17)
  - Bob Calls Kay's Bluff (Show #97, v.III, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 5/16/57. Draft script dated: 3/22/57. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil / Wesson, Dick (Box 16)
  - Bob Collins, Jr. (Show #40, v.IX)
    - Aired: 12/8/55. Draft script dated: 10/14/55. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Manhoff, Bill * Cowley, Bill (Box 18)
  - Bob Enters Photography Contest (Show #95, v.II, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 5/2/57. Draft script dated: 3/15/57. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil / Wesson, Dick (Box 16)
  - Bob Escapes Schultzy's Trap (Show #91, v.I, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 4/4/57. Draft script dated: 2/8/57. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil / Wesson, Dick (Box 16)
  - Bob Falls In Love (Show #33, v.IX)
    - Draft script dated: 8/26/55. Writer(s): Henning, Paul * Manhoff, Bill (Box 18)
  - Bob For Mayor (Show #99, v.III, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 5/30/57. Draft script dated: 4/1/57. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil / Wesson, Dick (Box 16)
  - Bob Gets Out-Uncled (Show #100, v.IV, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 6/6/57. Draft script dated: 4/12/57. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil / Wesson, Dick (Box 16)
  - Bob Gets Schultzy In Pictures (Show #102, v.IV, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 10/3/57. Draft script dated: 4/25/57. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Wesson, Dick (Box 16)
  - Bob Goes Fishing..Gets Caught (Show #96, v.III, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 5/9/57. Draft script dated: 3/21/57. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil / Wesson, Dick (Box 16)
  - Bob In Surgery (Show #153, v.IV, 1957-58)
    - Draft script dated: 10/30/58. Writer(s): Henning, Paul * Wesson, Dick (Box 16)
  - Bob Meets Miss Sweden (Show #94, v.II, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 4/25/57. Draft script dated: 3/7/57. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil / Wesson, Dick (Box 16)
  - Bob Meets Schultzy's Cousin (Show #88, v.I, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 3/14/57. Draft script dated: 1/4/57. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil / Wesson, Dick (Box 16)
  - Bob Meets the Mortons (spec. guests Burns and Allen)(Show #89, 1957)(in B & A v.229-233)
    - Aired: 3/21/57. Draft script dated: 1/16/57. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil / Wesson, Dick (Box 10)
  - Bob Picks A College (Show #85, v.I, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 2/21/57. Draft script dated: 12/13/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil / Wesson, Dick (Box 16)
  - Bob Plays Cupid (Show #20, v.VII)
    - Aired: 5/8/55. Draft script dated: 3/26/55. Writer(s): Henning, Paul * Manhoff, Bill (Box 17)
  - Bob Plays Gigolo (Show #92, v.II, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 4/11/57. Draft script dated: 2/14/57. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil / Wesson, Dick (Box 16)
  - Bob Tangles With Ruthie (Show #84, v.I, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 2/14/57. Draft script dated: 12/13/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil / Wesson, Dick (Box 16)
  - Bob to the Rescue or Unhand My Sister, You Cad (Show #15, v.VII)
    - Aired: 4/10/55. Draft script dated: 2/11/55. Writer(s): Henning, Paul * Manhoff, Bill (Box 17)
  - Bob's Birthday (Show #24, v.VIII)
    - Aired: 6/12/55. Draft script dated: 5/7/55. Writer(s): Henning, Paul * Manhoff, Bill (Box 17)
  - Bob's Economy Wave (Show #93, v.II, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 4/18/57. Draft script dated: 3/1/57. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil / Wesson, Dick (Box 16)
  - Bob's One Day To Relax (Show #38, odd 1955-56)
    - Aired: 11/24/55. Draft script dated: 9/30/55. Writer(s): Henning, Paul * Alsberg, Arthur (Box 18)
  - Boys Join Up, The (Show #61, v.V)
    - Aired: 5/10/56. Draft script dated: 3/16/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Shirl (Box 17)
  - Con Man, The (Show #58, v.X)
    - Aired: 4/12/56. Draft script dated: 2/24/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Cowley, Bill * Gordon, Shirl (Box 18)
  - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Cummings (Show #16, v.VII)
    - Aired: 4/3/55. Draft script dated: 2/15/55. Writer(s): Henning, Paul * Manhoff, Bill (Box 17)
  - El Lobo Strikes Again (Show #27, v.VIII)
    - Aired: 7/10/55. Draft script dated: 5/30/55. Writer(s): Henning, Paul * Manhoff, Bill (Box 17)
  - El Lobo Strikes Again and Again (Show #32, v.IX)
    - Writer(s): Henning, Paul (Box 18)
  - Fallen Idol, The (Show #53, v.XI)
    - Aired: 3/8/56. Draft script dated: 1/27/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Cowley, Bill * Gordon, Shirl (Box 18)
  - Grandpa Meets Zsa Zsa (Show #66, v.VI)
    - Aired: 10/4/56. Draft script dated: 5/4/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil (Box 17)
  - Long Live the King (Show #51, v.XI)
    - Aired: 2/23/56. Draft script dated: 1/14/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Cowley, Bill * Gordon, Shirl (Box 18)
  - Margaret Becomes Sadie Thompson (Show #65, v.VI)
    - Aired: 6/21/56. Draft script dated: 4/27/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil (Box 17)
  - Return of the Wolf or Absense Makes the Heart Grow Fonda (Show #25, v.VIII)
    - Aired: 6/19/55. Draft script dated: 5/10/55. Writer(s): Henning, Paul * Manhoff, Bill (Box 17)
  - Schultzy Says No (Show #73, odd 1955-56)
    - Aired: 11/22/56. Draft script dated: 9/28/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil (Box 18)
  - Scramble For Grandpa (Show #63, v.V)
    - Aired: 5/24/56. Draft script dated: 4/13/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil (Box 17)
  - Sergeant Wore Shirts, The (Show #62, v.V)
    - Aired: 5/10/56. Draft script dated: 3/23/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Shuken, Phil (Box 17)
  - Snowbound (Show #50, v.XI)
    - Aired: 2/16/56. Draft script dated: 12/17/55. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Gordon, Shirl * Cowley, Bill (Box 18)
  - Trouble With Henry, The (Show #59, v.X)
    - Aired: 4/19/56. Draft script dated: 3/2/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Cowley, Bill * Gordon, Shirl (Box 18)
  - Two Many Women (Show #49, v.XI)
    - Aired: 2/9/56. Draft script dated: 12/13/55. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Cowley, Bill * Gordon, Shirl (Box 18)
  - Uncle Bob-Bob (Show #22, v.VIII)
    - Aired: 5/29/55. Draft script dated: 4/22/55. Writer(s): Henning, Paul * Manhoff, Bill (Box 17)
  - Wedding, Wedding, Who's Having the Wedding? (Show #37, v.IX)
    - Aired: 11/17/55. Draft script dated: 8/23/55. Writer(s): Henning, Paul * Cowley, William (Box 18)
  - Wolf Who Came To Dinner, The (Show #54, v.XI)
    - Aired: 3/15/56. Draft script dated: 1/28/56. Writer(s): Henning, Paul / Cowley, Bill * Gordon, Shirl (Box 18)
- GEORGE BURNS AND GRACIE ALLEN SHOW, THE
  - $15,000 Error, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #231, 1957)
    - Aired: 3/4/57. Draft script dated: 1/23/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 10)
  - Accident, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #279, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 2/3/58. Draft script dated: 12/18/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - African Hunter, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #267, 1957)
    - Aired: 11/11/57. Draft script dated: 9/11/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 11)
  - Aptitude Test, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #225, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 1/28/57. Draft script dated: 12/12/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 10)
  - Big Stamp Robbery, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #215, 1956)
    - Aired: 11/12/56. Draft script dated: 9/26/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 9)
  - Blanche Gets a Jury Notice (incl. afterpiece) (Show #288, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 4/14/58. Draft script dated: 2/26/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - Blanche's Mother Arrives (incl. afterpiece) (Show #244, 1957)
    - Aired: 6/3/57. Draft script dated: 5/1/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 11)
  - Box of Cigars, A (incl. afterpiece) (Show #270, 1957)
    - Aired: 12/2/57. Draft script dated: 10/2/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 11)
  - Christmas In Jail (incl. afterpiece) (Show #221, 1956)
    - Aired: 12/24/56. Draft script dated: 11/7/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, Williams (Box 9)
  - Costume Party, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #222, 1956)
    - Aired: 12/31/56. Draft script dated: 11/14/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 9)
  - English Tea, An (incl. afterpiece) (Show #264, 1957)
    - Aired: 10/21/57. Draft script dated: 8/14/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 11)
  - Exchange Student, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #299, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 12/15/58. Draft script dated: 6/4/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 13)
  - Fighting for Happiness (incl. afterpiece) (Show #229, 1957)
    - Aired: 2/18/57. Draft script dated: 1/9/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 10)
  - Fortune Teller, The (added scene in v.229-233) (Show #228, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 2/11/57. Draft script dated: 1/23/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 10)
  - Fortune Teller, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #228, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 2/11/57. Draft script dated: 12/26/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 10)
  - Frozen Passion (incl. afterpiece) (Show #284, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 3/17/58. Draft script dated: 1/29/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - General, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #261, 1957)
    - Aired: 9/30/57. Draft script dated: 7/24/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 11)
  - George's Grey Suit (incl. afterpiece) (Show #216, 1956)
    - Aired: 11/26/56. Draft script dated: 10/3/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 9)
  - Girl Behind the Perfume Counter, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #219, 1956)
    - Aired: 12/10/56. Draft script dated: 10/24/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 9)
  - Going to Palm Springs (incl. afterpiece) (Show #226, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 1/28/57. Draft script dated: 12/12/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 10)
  - Going to Palm Springs (added scene in v.229-233)(Show #226, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 1/28/57. Draft script dated: 12/12/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 10)
  - Gracie and the Bullfighter (incl. afterpiece) (Show #223, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 1/7/57. Draft script dated: 11/21/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 9)
  - Gracie and the Jury (incl. afterpiece) (Show #289, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 4/28/58. Draft script dated: 3/19/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - Gracie is Brilliant (incl. afterpiece) (Show #282, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 3/3/58. Draft script dated: 1/15/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - Grammar School Dance, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #298, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 9/8/58. Draft script dated: 5/21/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 13)
  - High Blood Pressure (incl. afterpiece) (Show #285, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 3/24/58. Draft script dated: 2/5/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - Hole in the Carpet, A (incl. afterpiece) (Show #272, 1957)
    - Aired: 12/16/57. Draft script dated: 10/9/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - Home Graduation, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #243, 1957)
    - Aired: 5/27/57. Draft script dated: 4/24/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 10)
  - How to Wrap a Mink (incl. afterpiece) (Show #273, 1957)
    - Aired: 12/23/57. Draft script dated: 10/30/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - Hypnotizing Gracie (incl. afterpiece) (Show #281, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 2/24/58. Draft script dated: 1/8/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - Initiation, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #213, 1956)
    - Aired: 11/5/56. Draft script dated: 9/12/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 9)
  - Interview, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #212, 1956)
    - Aired: 10/29/56. Draft script dated: 9/5/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 9)
  - Invitation to the Party (incl. afterpiece) (Show #274, 1957)
    - Aired: 12/30/57. Draft script dated: 11/13/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - Japanese Texan, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #280, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 2/10/58. Draft script dated: 12/24/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - June Wedding, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #296, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 6/16/58. Draft script dated: 5/14/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 13)
  - Little Fight, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #268, 1957)
    - Aired: 11/18/57. Draft script dated: 9/18/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 11)
  - Locked Out (incl. afterpiece) (Show #294, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 6/2/58. Draft script dated: 4/30/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 13)
  - Marital Mix-Up, A (incl. afterpiece) (Show #245, 1957)
    - Aired: 6/10/57. Draft script dated: 5/8/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 11)
  - Matrimonial Bureau, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #227, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 2/4/57. Draft script dated: 12/19/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 10)
  - McAfee and the Manicurist (incl. afterpiece) (Show #277, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 1/20/58. Draft script dated: 12/4/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - Misery Loves Company (incl. afterpiece) (Show #271, 1957)
    - Aired: 12/9/57. Draft script dated: 10/23/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - Mrs.Sohmers Needs A Psychologist (Show #195, 1956)
    - Aired: 9/1/56. Draft script dated: 5/23/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 9)
  - Pain in the Back?, A (incl. afterpiece) (Show #247, 1957)
    - Aired: 6/24/57. Draft script dated: 5/22/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 11)
  - Plumber's Friend, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #233, 1957)
    - Aired: 3/18/57. Draft script dated: 2/6/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 10)
  - Publicity Marriage, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #287, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 4/7/58. Draft script dated: 2/19/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - Publicity Romance, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #239, 1957)
    - Aired: 4/29/57. Draft script dated: 3/20/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 10)
  - Questions and Answers (Show #193, 1956)
    - Aired: 6/11/56. Draft script dated: 5/9/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 9)
  - Refrigerator Salesman, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #218, 1956)
    - Aired: 12/3/56. Draft script dated: 10/17/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 9)
  - Return to California (incl. afterpiece) (Show #209, 1956)
    - Aired: 10/8/56. Draft script dated: 8/15/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 9)
  - Ring, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #232, 1957)
    - Aired: 3/11/57. Draft script dated: 1/30/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 10)
  - Ronnie Finds a Friend an Apartment (incl. afterpiece) (Show #276, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 1/13/58. Draft script dated: 11/27/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - Ronnie Goes Into The Army (incl. afterpiece) (Show #293, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 5/26/58. Draft script dated: 4/23/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 13)
  - Ronnie Makes a Record (incl. afterpiece) (Show #290, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 5/5/58. Draft script dated: 3/26/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 13)
  - Ronnie Quits College Because His Father Goes Broke (incl.afterpiece) (Show #220, 1956)
    - Aired: 12/17/56. Draft script dated: 10/31/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 9)
  - Ronnie's Bashful (incl. afterpiece) (Show #214, 1956)
    - Aired: 11/12/56. Draft script dated: 9/19/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 9)
  - Ronnie's Boat (incl. afterpiece) (Show #241, 1957)
    - Aired: 5/13/57. Draft script dated: 4/10/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 10)
  - Ronnie's Fan Club (incl. afterpiece) (Show #283, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 3/10/58. Draft script dated: 1/22/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - Ronnie's Royalty Check (incl. afterpiece) (Show #291, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 5/12/58. Draft script dated: 4/2/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 13)
  - Ronnie's Twenty-One (extra scene) (Show #248, 1957)
    - Aired: 7/1/57. Draft script dated: 5/29/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 11)
  - Ronnie's Twenty-One (incl. afterpiece) (Show #248, 1957)
    - Aired: 7/1/57. Draft script dated: 5/29/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 11)
  - September and May (incl. afterpiece) (Show #265, 1957)
    - Aired: 10/28/57. Draft script dated: 9/21/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 11)
  - Shakespearean Paper, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #210, 1956)
    - Aired: 10/15/56. Draft script dated: 8/22/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 9)
  - Softening the Professor (incl. afterpiece) (Show #286, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 3/31/58. Draft script dated: 2/12/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - Star Maker, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #266, 1957)
    - Aired: 11/4/57. Draft script dated: 8/28/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 11)
  - Stolen Car, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #275, 1957)
    - Aired: 1/6/58. Draft script dated: 11/20/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - Summer School (incl. afterpiece) (Show #297, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 6/23/58. Draft script dated: 5/28/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman, Burns, William (Box 13)
  - Termites, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #230, 1957)
    - Aired: 2/25/57. Draft script dated: 1/16/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 10)
  - Texan Italian, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #263, 1957)
    - Aired: 10/14/57. Draft script dated: 8/7/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 11)
  - Texan Lady Macbeth, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #240, 1957)
    - Aired: 4/29/57. Draft script dated: 3/20/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 10)
  - Too Many Fathers (incl. afterpiece) (Show #278, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 1/27/58. Draft script dated: 12/11/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 12)
  - Too Much Pot Roast (incl. afterpiece) (Show #262, 1957)
    - Aired: 10/7/57. Draft script dated: 7/31/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 11)
  - Trip to Tahiti, A (incl. afterpiece) (Show #242, 1957)
    - Aired: 5/20/57. Draft script dated: 4/17/57. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 10)
  - Ugly Duckling, The (incl. afterpiece) (Show #224, 1956-57)
    - Aired: 1/14/57. Draft script dated: 11/28/56. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 10)
  - Visit From Charles Vidor, A (incl. afterpiece) (Show #292, 1957-58)
    - Aired: 5/19/58. Draft script dated: 4/16/58. Writer(s): Helm, Harvey / Fowler, Keith * Paul, Norman / Burns, William (Box 13)
  - Von Zell's Raises (incl. afterpiece) (Show #217, 1956)